Herz, John H.; Papers ger015
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Texts of lectures, conference materials; course notes & lectures, 7; 133 file folders
  - Miscellaneous materials from lectures attended by Herz, 7.98 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 38-50)
    - American Political Science Association, annual meetings, 1957-1961 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 41)
    - Congress for Cultural Freedom Conference, 1960 June 16-1960 June 20 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 42)
      Includes papers by: Herbert Lüthy, Raymond Aron, Bertrand de Jouvenel, Michael Polanyi.
    - Institute for Professors of International Studies. U.S. Mission to the U.N., 1965 April 14-1965 April 15 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 43)
    - Korcula, Yugoslavia conference, 1968 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 44)
      Includes papes by: Rudi Supek, Arnold Kuenzli, Agnes Heller, Howard L. Parsons, Ernst Fischer, Michael Landmann, Tordai Zador.
    - Marburg conference, 1968 June 27-1968 June 29 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 45)
      Includes papers by: Dieter Senghaas, Klaus Faupel, Karl Kaiser, Kurt Tudyka.
    - Organizing the Euro-American System. Conference in Arnoldshain, 1975 January 27-1975 January 30 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 46)
      Includes papers & outlines by: Frans A. M. Alting von Geusau, David P. Calleo, Ernst Otto Czempiel, Guy de Carmoy, A. J. R. Groom, Wilhelm Hankel, Pierre Hassner, Rainer Hellmann, Manfred Knapp, Werner Link, J. S. Nye, Dankwart A. Rustow, Roger Williams.
    - Sixth International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences (ICUS), San Francisco, CA, 1977 November 25-1977 November 27 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 47)
    - CUNY Political Science Conference, 1977 December 02-1977 December 03 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 48)
      Includes papers by: Jacques Fumerand, Melvin Mutzner.
    - The Seventh International Conference on the Unity of the Sciences (ICUS), Boston, MA, 1978 November 24-1978 November 26 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 49)
    - XII IPSA World Congress, Rio de Janeiro, 1982 August 08-1982 August 14 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 50)
  - Symposium on Political and Psychological Aspects of Soviet-American Relations, Columbia University, 1983 May 08 (Box 14 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 51)
  - Course notes, syllabi, reading lists, exam questions, 7.100 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 1-22)
    - American Foreign Policies, ca. 1940 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 1)
    - American Foreign Policies, 1951-1953 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 2)
    - American Foreign Policy Seminar, 1975 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 3)
    - American Government, 1952-1960 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 4)
    - American Political Thought, 1956-1957 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 5)
    - Central European Government, 1972-1975 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 6)
    - Comparative Government: Democratic Systems, 1960s (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 7)
    - Comparative Politics, 1975-1976 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 8)
    - Futurology, 1973 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 9)
    - History of Political Theory, 1960-1961 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 10)
    - International Law, 1940s (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 11)
    - International Law, 1966-1977 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 12)
    - International Politics: syllabi, exam questions, 1951-1976 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 13)
    - International Politics: notes, Undated (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 14)
    - Modern Political Theory, 1949-1965 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 15)
    - Political Philosophy, ca. 1960 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 16)
    - Theories of International Relations, 1959; 1974 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 17)
    - Theory of Democracy, 1962 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 18)
    - Grundlagen der internationalen Politik. Freie Universität Berlin, 1981 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 19)
    - Aussenpolitische Ideologien, 1981 Summer (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 20)
    - Weltpolitik zwischen Konflikt und Ausgleich, 1981 Summer (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 21)
    - Syllabi, Exam Questions, 1948-1967 (Box 15 (7-Texts of lectures, conference materials; ), Folder 22)
- Publications by colleagues, other scholars, 8; 259 file folders
  This series contains primarily reprints sent to Herz by colleagues, but also contains some typescripts of conference and other papers. Represented in this series are a substantial collection of publications by Ernst Otto Czempiel, Ossip K. Flechthiem, Gerhard Herz (brother of John Herz) and Otto Kirchheimer.
  - Wolfgang Abendroth, Undated; 4 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 23)
  - René Albrecht-Carrié, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 24)
  - Chadwick F. Alger, Undated; 1 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 25)
  - Gabriel A. Almond, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 26)
    RAND Corporation working paper.
  - Hannah Arendt. Mimeographed text, Undated (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 27)
  - Helga Aschaffenburg, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 28)
  - Hans Aufricht, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 29)
  - William Osgood Aydelotte, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 30)
  - Allen B. Ballard Jr., Undated; Mimeographed typescript (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 31)
  - P. A. Baran, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 32)
  - A. Bargman, Undated; Mimeographed typescript (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 33)
  - Enno Bartels, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 34)
  - Victor Basiuk, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 35)
  - Bernard Bellush; Jewel Bellush, Undated; Reprint, typescript (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 36)
  - Joseph W. Bendersky, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 37)
  - Anthony T. Bouscaren, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 38)
  - Karl Dietrich Bracher, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 39)
  - Randolph L. Braham, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 40)
    Reprints are sections from books; photocopies of clippings; typescripts of memoirs.
  - Ralph Braibanti, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 41)
  - Beatrice Baude, Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 42)
    Photocopies of clippings.
  - Gerard Braunthal, Undated; 5 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 43)
  - Arnold Brecht, Undated; 3 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 44)
  - Wilfried von Bredow, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 45)
  - Henry L. Bretton, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 46)
  - Bernard E. Brown, Undated; 4 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 47)
  - Frederic S. Burin, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 48)
  - Werner J. Cahnman, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 49)
  - Joel Carmichael, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 50)
  - Honoré M. Catudal Jr., Undated; 2 (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 51)
  - Sok Chough, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 52)
  - Carl Q. Christol, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 53)
  - Cole Taylor, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 54)
  - David P. Conradt, Undated; Reprint (Box 15 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 55)
  - P. E. Corbett, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 1)
  - Richard Cox, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 2)
  - Ernst Otto Czempiel, 1965-1989; 10 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 3)
  - Ernst Otto Czempiel, 1991-2004; Typescript; 11 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 4)
  - Ralf Dahrendorf, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 5)
  - John A. Davis, Undated; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 6)
  - Henry Delfiner, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 7)
  - Karl W. Deutsch, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 8)
  - Martin Domke, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 9)
  - Volker Dotterweich, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 10)
  - Ivo Duchacek, Undated; 5; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 11)
  - Kurt Düwell, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 12)
  - Edward Mead Earle, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 13)
  - Lewis J. Edinger, Undated; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 14)
  - Horst Ehmke, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 15)
  - Henry W. Ehrmann, Undated; 3 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 16)
  - Salo Engel, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 17)
  - Frederick C. Engelmann, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 18)
  - Klaus Epstein, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 19)
  - Amitai Etzioni, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 20)
  - Richard A. Falk, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 21)
  - Seymour Maxwell Finger, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 22)
  - Lawrence S. Finkelstein, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 23)
  - Klaus Fischer, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 24)
  - Lili Faktor Flechtheim, Undated; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 25)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim, 1956-1980; Clippings (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 26)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim, 1936-1949; 8 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 27)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim, 1952-1958; 9 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 28)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim, 1962-1965; 15 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 29)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim, 1966-1969; 17 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 30)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim, 1970-1988; 14 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 31)
  - Ossip K. Flechtheim. Obituaries, 1998 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 32)
  - Peter J. Fliess, Undated; 3 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 33)
  - Jacques Fomerand, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 34)
  - William T. R. Fox; Annette Baker Fox, Undated; 5 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 35)
  - Elke Frank, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 36)
  - Daniel Frei, Undated; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 37)
  - Herbert Frenzel, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 38)
  - John H. E. Fried, Undated; 2; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 39)
  - Carl J. Friedrich, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 40)
  - Ernst Friesenhahn, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 41)
  - Morton J. Frisch, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 42)
  - Klaus Jürgen Gantzel, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 43)
  - Richard N. Gardner, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 44)
  - Ethan Geto, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 45)
  - David G. Gil, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 46)
  - Felix Gilbert, Undated; 4 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 47)
  - Dietrich Goldschmidt, Undated; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 48)
  - Hans Goldschmidt, Undated; 2 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 49)
  - Dov Goldstein, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 50)
  - R. K. Gooch, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 51)
  - Harrison G. Gough; Giuseppe DiPalma, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 52)
  - Martin Greiffenhagen, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 53)
  - William E. Griffith, Undated; Reprint (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 54)
  - Leo Gross, Undated; 3 (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 55)
  - Otto Grüters, Undated; Typescript (Box 16 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 56)
  - Ernst B. Haas, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 1)
  - Christian Hacke, Undated; 7; 1; Clippings (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 2)
  - Dennis Hale, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 3)
  - Jerome Hall, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 4)
  - Edvard Hambro, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 5)
  - Sungjoo Han, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 6)
  - Arthur M. Hanhardt Jr., Undated; Reprint, typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 7)
  - Wolfram F. Hanrieder, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 8)
  - Abram L. Harris, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 9)
  - Arnold J. Heidenheimer, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 10)
  - Robert L. Heilbroner, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 11)
  - F. Hellendall, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 12)
  - Samuel Hendel, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 13)
  - Alan K. Henrikson, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 14)
  - Ferdinand A. Hermens, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 15)
  - Gerhard Herz, 1946-1979; 11 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 16)
  - Gerhard Herz, 1983-1990; 10 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 17)
    Program notes.
  - Gerhard Herz, Undated (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 18)
    Clippings and articles about.
  - Felix Hirsch, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 19)
  - Helmut Hirsch, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 20)
  - Stanley Hoffmann, Undated; 3 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 21)
  - Hajo Holborn, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 22)
  - Louise W. Holborn, Undated; 3 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 23)
  - Thomas Ford Hoult, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 24)
  - Edwin C. Hoyt, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 25)
  - Michael C. Hudson, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 26)
  - Erich Hula, Undated; 4 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 27)
  - Warren F. Ilchman, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 28)
  - Hans-Adolf Jacobsen, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 29)
  - Helio Jaquaribe, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 30)
  - Oscar I. Janowsky, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 31)
  - Inge Jens, Undated; Reprint, typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 32)
  - Robert Jervis, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 33)
  - Whittle Johnston, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 34)
  - Hans Jonas, Undated; 4; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 35)
  - Ludwig W. Kahn, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 36)
  - Robert A. Kann, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 37)
  - Karl W. Kapp, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 38)
  - Thomas G. Karis, Undated; 4; 8 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 39)
  - Hans Kelsen, Undated; 5 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 40)
  - Mario Keßler, Undated; Typescript (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 41)
  - Gottfried-Karl Kindermann, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 42)
  - Roger P. Kingsley, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 43)
  - Otto Kirchheimer, Undated; 9 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 44)
  - Otto Kirchheimer. Newspaper clippings, 1929-1933 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 45)
  - Otto Kirchheimer, 1928-1956; 11 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 46)
  - Otto Kirchheimer, 1957-1967; 14 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 47)
  - Norman Kogan, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 48)
  - Hans Kohn, Undated; 2 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 49)
  - Donald P. Kommers, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 50)
  - Leonard Krieger, Undated; 4 (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 51)
  - Ekkehart Krippendorff, Undated; Reprint (Box 17 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 52)
  - J. J. Lador-Lederer, Undated; 3 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 1)
  - Martin Landau, Undated; 3 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 2)
  - Harry Lazer, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 3)
  - Richard Ned Lebow, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 4)
  - Hongkoo Lee; Chong-Wook Chung, Undated; Typescript (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 5)
  - Rensselaer W. Lee III, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 6)
  - Gerhard Leibholz, Undated; 5 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 7)
  - George Lenczowski, Undated; 3 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 8)
  - Howard H. Lentner, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 9)
  - Mordechai M. Levy, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 10)
  - Jean Atherton Flexner Lewinson, Undated; Bound typescript (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 11)
  - Guenter Lewy, Undated; 5; 1 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 12)
  - George Lichtheim, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 13)
  - Arend Lijphart, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 14)
  - Werner Link, Undated; 4 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 15)
  - Gerhard Loewenberg, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 16)
  - Karl Loewenstein, Undated; 8 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 17)
  - Richard Löwenthal, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 18)
  - Peter Ludz, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 19)
  - Herbert Marcuse, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 20)
  - Vojtech Mastny, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 21)
  - Hans Mayer, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 22)
  - Peter McDonough; Antonio Lopez Pina, Undated; Typescript (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 23)
  - Robert McGeehan, Undated; Typescript (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 24)
  - George McKenna, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 25)
  - Horst Mendershausen, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 26)
  - Peter H. Merkl, Undated; 2; 1 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 27)
  - Hans Meyerhof, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 28)
  - Stefanie Middendorf, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 29)
  - Robert W. Miller, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 30)
  - Ben Mollov, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 31)
  - Clement H. Moore, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 32)
  - Hans J. Morgenthau, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 33)
  - Fritz Morstein Marx, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 34)
  - Fritz Münch, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 35)
  - Martin C. Needler, Undated; Typescript (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 36)
  - Franz Neumann, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 37)
  - Reinhold Niebuhr, Undated; Typescript (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 38)
  - Donald E. Nuechterlein, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 39)
  - Felix E. Oppenheim, Undated; 5; 1 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 40)
  - Manuel Medina Ortega, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 41)
  - Henry M. Pachter, Undated; 6 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 42)
  - Ingo Peters, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 43)
  - Raymond Polin, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 44)
  - Arnold H. Price, Undated; 2 (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 45)
  - Donald J. Puchala, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 46)
  - William E. Rappard, Undated; Reprint (Box 18 (8-Publications by colleagues, other ), Folder 47)